该死
Oh, shit.
已经过了一天半了
It's been a day and a half.
他们也什么都没找到
They didn't find any either.
- 你怎么知道 - 我就是知道
- How do you know? - I know.
我们还有多远
How much longer we got?
60英里
60 miles.
我问的不是这个
I wasn't talking about that.
《行尸走肉》
没油了 跟之前那辆一样
We're out, just like the other one.
那我们就走吧
So we walk.
我们状态不佳
We're not at our strongest.
等安顿好了再去干掉它们
We'll get 'em when it's best.
找个高地之类的
High ground, something like that.
它们哪里都会不去
They're not going anywhere.
离开亚特兰大已经三周了
It's been three weeks since Atlanta.
我知道你在那里失去了某些东西
I know you lost something back there.
她饿了
She's hungry.
她没事
She's okay.
她会没事的
She's going to be okay.
我们得找到水 食物
We need to find water, food.
我们在路上会有所发现的
We'll hit something in the road.
迟早会下雨
It's gonna rain sooner or later.
我去转一圈
I'm gonna head out.
看看能找到什么
See what I can find.
别去太久
Hey, don't be too long.
我跟你一起去
I'll go with you.
我自己就行
I got it.
你要阻止我吗
You gonna stop me?
找水时我找到了这个
Found this when we were looking for water.
这是什么
What is it?
我觉得这东西以前可以放音乐
I think it used to play music.
现在坏了
It's broken.
谢谢 卡尔
Thanks, Carl.
我觉得你也许会喜欢
I thought you might like it.
我以前开玩笑说这些东西是苦行者时代
I used to joke these things were leftovers
遗留下来的粗毛衬衣
from the days of hair shirts.
教堂实际上…
The church actually made...
用粗毛做过衬衣
shirts out of hair.
如果你穿上 就能靠受苦
So if you wore it, you could atone
赎一点罪
just a little for your sins.
我知道粗毛衬衣是什么
I know what a hair shirt is.
我爸爸信教
My daddy was religious.
我以前也信
I used to be.
如果你想聊聊
If you ever want to talk
你父亲的事
about your father
或者贝丝的事…
or about Beth...
请你住嘴
Please, stop.
如果你准备好了 我洗耳恭听
Whenever you're ready, I'm here.
你都没见过他们
You never even met them.
- 我知道你很痛苦 - 你知道个屁
- I know you're in pain. - You don't know shit.
你是个牧师
You had a job.
你本该拯救你的信众 对吧
You were there to save your flock, right?
但你没有
But you didn't.
你躲起来了
You hid.
别装作这一切没有发生过
Don't act like that didn't happen.
我们可以干掉它们
We can take 'em.
瑞克说的没错
Rick's right.
我们的气力所剩无几
We barely have anything left.
没必要现在用尽
No use in spending it all now.
我可以干掉它们
I can take 'em.
你哥哥当时也很愤怒
Your brother was pissed, too,
在他失去了爱人之后
after what he lost.
- 这让他变得愚蠢 - 我俩不一样
- It made him stupid. - We are not the same.
我们从来都不一样
We never were.
但还是一样的
But it's still the same.
就是一样的
It just is.
有发现吗
Anything?
没有 太干了
No, it's too dry.
这里什么也没有
There ain't nothing here.
也许我们应该往回走了
Maybe we should start back.
你走吧
You go.
我觉得她救了我一命
I think she saved my life.
她也救了你一命 不是吗
She saved your life, too, right?
这是她的遗物
It was hers.
我们没有死
We're not dead.
这是你说的
That's what you said.
你没有死
You're not dead.
我了解你
I know you.
我跟你不一样 我不能让自己…
We're different. I can't let myself...
但是你…
But you...
我了解你
I know you.
你必须要直面你的感受
You have to let yourself feel it.
你会的
You will.
萨沙
Sasha.
保持队形 从侧面掩护她
Stay in line. Flank her.
控制住局势
Keep it controlled.
计划被搅乱了
Plan just got dicked.
住手 离开这里
Stop. Just get out of here.
我说了让你住手
I told you to stop.
爸爸
Dad,
看
look.
我去林子里
I'm gonna head into the woods,
绕一圈看看
circle back.
- 我能跟你一起去吗 - 不行
- May I come with? - No.
我自己去
No, just me.
玛姬
Maggie.
里面有…
There's one...
里面有只行尸
there's one in there.
我关上了 它还在里面
And I shut it and it's still in there.
好的
Okay.
我们走吧
Let's go.
我们找到的只有酒吗
So all we found was booze?
是的
Yeah.
喝酒没用的
It's not gonna help.
他知道的
He knows that.
只会让事情变得更糟
It's gonna make it worse.
是的
Yes, it is.
他是个成年人了
He's a grown man.
我真心不觉得事情还能变得更糟
And I truly do not know if things can get worse.
能的
They can.
你哥哥
Your brother...
他想帮我
he tried to help me.
我不知道自己能不能活下去
I don't know if I'm gonna make it.
那你就活不下去
Then you won't.
别想了
Don't think.
吃东西吧
Just eat.
- 玛姬 喝点水吧 - 不
- Maggie, take a drink. - No.
好吧
Okay.
那跟我聊聊天怎么样
How about you just talk to me?
我没想到她还活着
I never thought she was alive.
我没想到
I just didn't.
爸爸去世后 我不知道
After Daddy, I don't know
我做不到了
if I couldn't.
听达里尔说过之后
And after what Daryl said,
我希望她仍在某处活着
I hoped she was out there, alive.
然后发现她确实还活着
And then finding out that she was
可当天就失去了她
and then she wasn't in the same day...
看到她那样 简直…
Seeing her like that, it...
让我觉得一切都那么不真实
made it feel like none of it was ever really there.
以前
Before...
这只是我心头的阴影
this was just the dark part and...
现在我不知道自己能不能拼下去了
I don't know if I want to fight it anymore.
你能的
You do.
那才是你
That's who you are.
也许这是当今世界的诅咒
And maybe it's a curse nowadays,
但我不这么想
but I don't think so.
我们一路拼到现在
We fought to be here.
我们还得拼下去
And we have to keep fighting.
喝水吧
Drink.
喝酒只会让事情变得更糟
You know it'll just make things worse.
照你这个样子
The way you're going,
迟早会连累大家
you're what's gonna make things worse.
你还有我们这些朋友
You're with friends.
咱们不是朋友
We're not friends.
达里尔
Daryl.
不了 我不喝
No, I'm all right.
达里尔
Daryl.
不要
Don't.
我们可以一起活下去
we can make it together.
但只有我们在一起才能活下去
But we can only make it together.
告诉他们我去找水了
Tell them I went looking for water.
(朋友送上)
我们还能做什么
What else are we gonna do?
反正不能喝
Not this.
我们不知道是谁留下的
We don't know who left it.
如果这是陷阱 我们已经深陷其中了
If that's a trap, we already happen to be in it.
但是我愿意相信这真的是朋友送的
But I, for one, would like to think it is indeed from a friend.
如果不是呢 如果有人在水里下药了呢
What if it isn't? They put something in it?
- 尤金 - 你在干什么 老兄
- Eugene. - What are you doing, dude?
验证质量
Quality assurance.
我们不能喝
We can't.
上帝
Oh, God.
对不起 上帝
I'm sorry, my Lord.
大家都把包拿出来 所有能盛水的东西
Everybody get the bags. Anything you can find.
对不起
I'm sorry.
快点
Come on.
我们接着走吧
Let's keep moving.
- 附近有一个谷仓 - 在哪
- There's a barn. - Where?
(圣经)
她有枪
She had a gun.
本可以自杀的
She could have shot herself.
有些人无法放弃
Some people can't give up.
比如我们
Like us.
- 我试试 - 不行 太湿了
- I'll try. - No, too wet.
他会没事的
He's gonna be okay.
他的恢复能力
He bounces back
比我们强多了
more than any of us do.
我以前会为在这个世界成长的孩子感到难过
I used to feel sorry for kids that have to grow up now.
在这个末世
In this.
但是我觉得我错了
But I think I got it wrong.
成长就是适应这个世界
Growing up is getting used to the world.
这对他们来说更容易
This is easier for them.
世界不是这样的
This isn't the world.
不是的
This isn't it.
也许是
It might be.
也许
It might.
- 那是放弃 - 这是现实
- That's giving up. - It's reality.
在看到希望之前 我们得接受这一切
Until we see otherwise, this is what we have to live with.
我小时候
When I was a kid...
问过我爷爷是否在战争中杀过德国人
I asked my grandpa once if he ever killed any Germans in the war.
他不愿回答
He wouldn't answer.
他说那是成年人的事 所以
He said that was grown-up stuff, so...
于是我问他德国人有没有试图杀过他
so I asked if the Germans ever tried to kill him.
但他却异常沉默
But he got real quiet.
他说从他踏进敌占区那一刻就已经死了
He said he was dead the minute he stepped into enemy territory.
他每天醒来
Every day he woke up
就告诉自己 安息吧
and told himself, "Rest in peace.
然后起床去打仗吧
Now get up and go to war."
假装自己已经死了几年之后
And then after a few years of pretending he was dead...
他活着回来了
he made it out alive.
那大概就是诀窍吧
That's the trick of it, I think.
做我们该做的事
We do what we need to do
这样才能活下来
and then we get to live.
但无论我们在华府发现什么
But no matter what we find in DC,
我知道我们都会没事的
I know we'll be okay.
因为我们就是这样活下来的
Because this is how we survive.
我们告诉自己
We tell ourselves...
我们是行尸走肉
that we are the walking dead.
我们不是它们
We ain't them.
We're not them.
当然不是
We're not.
我们不是它们
We ain't them.
你该去睡会儿
You should get some sleep.
是啊
Yeah.
现在可以休息了
It's okay to rest now.
他很坚强
He was tough.
确实
He was.
她也是
So was she.
她自己不知道
She didn't know it,
但是她很坚强
but she was.
齿轮箱进了点沙子
The gearbox had some grit in it.
谢谢
Thank you.
跟我来
Come on.
瞧瞧
Look at this.
按理说我们也会死的
Should have torn us apart.
但是没有
It didn't.
我们为什么来这里
Why are we here?
为了这个
For this.
我懂你的意思
I see it.
诺亚 那个孩子
Noah, that kid...
他说他不知道自己能不能活下去
he said he didn't know if he can make it.
我也有同感
That's how I feel.
你会活下去
You're gonna make it.
我们俩都会活下去
Both of us, we will.
这才是最难的部分
That's the hard part.
达里尔修好了
Daryl fixed it.
没搞错吧
You got to be kidding me.
我无意打扰
I didn't mean to interrupt.
早上好
Good morning.
我叫亚伦
My name is Aaron.
我知道 陌生人很危险
I know, stranger danger.
但是我是你们的朋友
But I'm a friend.
我想和管事的人谈谈
I'd like to talk to the person in charge.
瑞克 对吗
Rick, right?
- 你怎么知道 - 为什么
- How do you know... - Why?
我有个好消息
I have good news.